Humane Borders records, 2000-2010 MS 471
University of Arizona
- Series I: Media Files, 2000-2010
  - Subseries 1: News clippings, June 1, 2000-December 29, 2009
    - Arizona Daily Wildcat, September 9, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 10, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Tucson Weekly, September 11, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - PBS Online NewsHour, September 17, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Narcosphere, September 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - U.N. Observer, September 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Boarderbeat.net, September 24, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Sydney Morning Herald, Smh.com.au, September 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - BBCMundo.com, October 2, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - KOLD.com, October 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 7, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Tucson Weekly, October 16, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Examiner.com, October 25, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 29, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - EkstraBladet.dk, October 29, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 30, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - The Reporter, October 30, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - The Daily Princetonian, November 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 11, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - National Alliance for Human Rights, November 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Excelsior, November 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - ABQJournal.com, November 24, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 26, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - La Cronica, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Milenio, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - La Jornada, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - El Sol de Mexico, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - La Cronica, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Cronica, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - El Universal, December 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - El Universal, December 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - El Universal, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - Cronica, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 339)
    - Milenio.com, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 340)
    - SDP El Sendero del Peje, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 341)
    - La Jornada, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 342)
    - La Jornada, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - Milenio, December 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - La Jornada, December 22, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 345)
    - Cronica, December 22, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - U.S. Customs and Border Protection, December 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 347)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 29, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 348)
    - The Builder, January 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - El Universal, January 11, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Nacional, January 11, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - La Jornada, January 11, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - New York Times, January 12, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - La Jornada, January 13, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Excelsior, January 13, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 14, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Milenio, January 23, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 25, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Green Valley News, January 29, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 31, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - ArgenPress.info, February 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 5, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Nogalesinternational.com, February 10, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - El Diario de Sonora, February 26, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - America, March 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - ISN ETH Zurich, March 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 11, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 31, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - The Tech, April 7, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Minnesota Daily, April 7, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Bakersfieldnow.com, April 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Chicago Tribune, April 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Lubbockonline.com, April 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Charleston Daily Mail, April 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - KPHO.com, April 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - KTAR.com, April 9, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 9, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 9, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 9, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Race Wire, April 10, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - InsideBayArea.com, April 11, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Reforma, April 12, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - The New York Times, April 14, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 14, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 26, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Green Valley News, April 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Commonweal, May 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - NY Times, May 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 17, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 17, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Barriozona, May 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - San Juan Diego Project, May 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Indigenous.Xicano, May 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Tucson Weekly, June 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - La Estrella de Tucson, June 5, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 6, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - La Cronica, June 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 16, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Barriozona, June 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - I.P.S. (Inter Press Service), June 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Wassertraeger, June 23, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Tucson Weekly, July 9, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 11, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 13, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - LA Times, July 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Arizona Republic, July 23, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - The Arizona Republic, July 23, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - American Jewish Society for Service, July 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Common Dreams, July 29, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 29, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 29, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 30, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 31, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Aregional.com, August 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 3, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - New York Times, August 6, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Tucson Weekly, August 6, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 7, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 10, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 12, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Center for Trade Policy Studies, August 13, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - La Jornada, August 15, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - The New York Times, August 16, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Yahoo! News, August 16, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - SignOnSanDiego.com, August 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Tucson Weekly, August 20, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Slate.com, August 21, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 23, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - AZCentral.com, August 24, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 25, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 30, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 31, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Borderbeat.net, August 31, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Examiner.com, September 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - NoMoreDeaths.org, September 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Green Valley News, September 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - KGUN9, September 27, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - KOLD News 13, September 27, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - The Washington Post, September 30, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - CommonDreams.org, September 30, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - MySanAntonio.com, October 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Enfoque, October 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Boarderbeat.net, October 5, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - AZCentral.com, October 6, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 7, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - DouglasDispatch.com, October 7, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - AZCentral.com, October 7, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 8, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 13, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - New York Times, October 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 22, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - The Ranger, San Antonio College, October 22, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 25, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - The Washington Times, October 25, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Desert News Network, October 26, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - LATimes.com, October 27, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Gospel1360online.com, October 27, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - La Jornada, November 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - The New Vision, November 1, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Borderbeat.net, November 2, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 3, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - ACLUAZ.org, November 3, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 4, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Imperial Valley Press, November 18, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Los Angeles Times, November 19, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 22, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - The Ekurd Voice, November 23, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - The New York Times, November 27, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - North County Times, November 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 28, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 29, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Media Lists, Undated (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Cartoons, [2001-2007] (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Cartoons, [2002-2009] (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Subseries 2: Audiovisual interviews with media and control files, 1996-2011
    This subseries is arranged by format, with each format arranged in rough chronological order. It contains the administrative control files, digital images and audiovisual material relating to immigration issues in the Southwestern United States borderlands and Humane Borders.
    - HB Admin Files Disc 1, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 1)
    - HB Admin Files Disc 2, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 2)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 1, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 3)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 2, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 4)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 3, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 5)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 4, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 6)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 5, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 7)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 6, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 8)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 7, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 9)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 8, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 10)
    - HB Still Photos Disc 9, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 11)
    - Print Article Index Water Data, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 12)
    - Video Index, April 2011 (Box 9, Othertype 13)
    - Chicano! Taking Back the Schools, 1996 (Box 10, Othertype 1)
    - Water Stations; 5 pm and 10 pm News, September 10, 2000 (Box 10, Othertype 2)
    - Well-Founded Fear, 2000 (Box 10, Othertype 3)
    - O'Reilly Factor: Moral Thing to do?, January 10, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 4)
    - Humane Borders in News clips, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Othertype 5)
    - 130 Migrants Apprehended, February 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 6)
    - First Deployment clips, March 19, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 7)
    - Migrant Encounter, April 18, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 8)
    - Death of 14, 5 pm, May 23, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 9)
    - Death of 12 Migrants, May 24, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 10)
    - News of 12 migrant deaths in one day, May 12, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 11)
    - Border Rancher, May 25, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 12)
    - Bodies shipped to Vera Cruz, May 31, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 13)
    - Robin Hoover at Studio for news cast, June 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 14)
    - Funeral Procession, May 31, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 15)
    - The New Frontier: High School Students Crossing, June 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 16)
    - HOT Water, June 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 17)
    - Border Patrol Strategy - Deaths in the Desert, July 3, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 18)
    - Senator Kolbe: resources on border, June 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 19)
    - Maria Hinojosa on the border, June 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 20)
    - Robin Hoover at Supervisor's Meeting, June 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 21)
    - Pima County $25,000 to HB 6-6-2001, June 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 22)
    - Pima County $25,000 to Humane Borders, June 7, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 23)
    - Humane Borders, AZ Illustrated, undated (Box 10, Othertype 24)
    - Humane Borders featured on KUAT, AZ Illustrated, June 13, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 25)
    - Death in the Desert, June 14, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 26)
    - Hardship on families of migrants, June 15, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 27)
    - INS witholds meals from migrants in detention, June 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 28)
    - Adventura en el disierto, 2007 (Box 10, Othertype 29)
    - Dangerous Crossing- Hoover, July 4, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 30)
    - Fidel Alonzo-Mireles, July 14, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 31)
    - McCain interview about Guest Worker, Amnesty, Open Border, July 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 32)
    - Mexican Workers, July 5, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 33)
    - Mateo Gomez at St Mary's Hospital, July 5, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 34)
    - Mateo Gomez Follow Up Story, July 6, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 35)
    - Hot water in water stations, July 7, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 36)
    - Attorney General Ashcroft in Yuma, July 10, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 37)
    - BP: Deaths in the Desert, August 29, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 38)
    - Water Stations at Rio Rico, August 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 39)
    - Ron Sanders interview about water stations, August 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 40)
    - Water stations and border news items, August 1, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 41)
    - Along the Line, September 21, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 42)
    - Simulation to crossing the desert, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 43)
    - Arizonans for Immigration Control, September 23, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 44)
    - Interview with Wes Bramhall, September 23, 2001 (Box 10, Othertype 45)
    - Water Stations Anniversary, February 24, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 46)
    - Water Stations, February 27, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 47)
    - BP Video Announcement, March 1, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 48)
    - Migrant Exhibition - Lost and Found, March 4, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 49)
    - Border Stories, 2005 (Box 10, Othertype 50)
    - Hoover at Buenos Aires NWR Water Stations, March 7, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 51)
    - Water Station Vandalism, March 9, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 52)
    - $40 Million Lawsuit, May 13, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 53)
    - $40 Million Lawsuit, May 15, 2002 (Box 10, Othertype 54)
    - Dangerous Crossings, May 19, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 1)
    - Destroying the desert, May 20, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 2)
    - Politically Incorrect, May 21, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 3)
    - Hannity and Colmes - Warning Map, May 12, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 4)
    - Death on a Friendly Border, June 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 5)
    - Mex. Public Service Announcements, June 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 6)
    - Water on the Reservation, June 9, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 7)
    - Samaritan Patrol, Hoover and Rick, July 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 8)
    - Samaritan Patrol- Jody Wert, July 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 9)
    - Samaritan Patrol, July 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 10)
    - Bill Walker Interview, August 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 11)
    - Deal with the Devil, August 8, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 12)
    - ACLU Hearing, August 23, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 13)
    - New Water Stations, August 23, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 14)
    - Humanitarian Assistance, August 28, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 15)
    - March for Migrants Memorial, September 29, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 16)
    - Enrique Marones, interview, October 1, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 17)
    - Phil Donohue Show, November 14, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 18)
    - Tombstone Militia, December 3, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 19)
    - Robin in studio - Tohono O' Odham comments, June 13, 2002 (Box 11, Othertype 20)
    - Anti-Immigrant Vigilantism 2003, October 7, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 21)
    - Report from the Border 2003 part 1, February 13, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 22)
    - Report from the Border 2003 part 2, February 13, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 23)
    - Invisible Mexicans of Deer Canyon, 2006 (Box 11, Othertype 24)
    - Lawsuit: 14 Migrant Deaths, May 6, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 25)
    - $14 Million lawsuit filed by migrant families, May 7, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 26)
    - Border Chaos, Heartland, May 16, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 27)
    - Water Station Dedication - Matthew Moove, July 20, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 28)
    - Christ Dies and Lives on the Border, August 1, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 29)
    - Paul Fuschini interview about warning posters, August 9, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 30)
    - Death Numbers, September 21, 2001 (Box 11, Othertype 31)
    - Paul Fuschini interviewed about warning posters, August 9, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 32)
    - Del Rio Deportation, September 10, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 33)
    - Gotas de Vida, October 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 34)
    - The Gatekeeper, October 16, 2003 (Box 11, Othertype 35)
    - Farmingville, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 36)
    - This is what Free Trade Looks Like, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 37)
    - More agents. Shell casings, February 1, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 38)
    - World News Tonight, May 18, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 39)
    - Illegal Crossing, May 18, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 40)
    - Water Stations, June 1, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 41)
    - The Big Story - John Gibson, July 13, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 42)
    - Terrorist Alley, August 16, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 43)
    - Board of Supervisors Meeting, September 7, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 44)
    - Hot Water - Physician, June 3, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 45)
    - Pima County Contract, September 8, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 46)
    - March for Migrants, September 26, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 47)
    - Memorial and March for Migrants, September 26, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 48)
    - Altar to Phoenix, December 17, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 49)
    - American Immigration, December 17, 2004 (Box 11, Othertype 50)
    - One Border One Body, 2008 (Box 11, Othertype 51)
    - Play Media for Humane Borders - Demo, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Othertype 52)
    - State or the county presentation, June 27, 2005 (Box 11, Othertype 53)
    - New Border Technologies, March 6, 2005 (Box 11, Othertype 54)
    - Dying to Live, March 25, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 1)
    - Arizona Illustrated, June 4, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 2)
    - Adventures with El Gordo, April 22, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 3)
    - Water Station Map, May 8, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 4)
    - Paul Fuschini Speaks on Warning Posters, May 11, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 5)
    - Warning Posters, May 12, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 6)
    - Warning Poster, May 20, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 7)
    - Warning Posters KOLD, May 20, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 8)
    - Salt Lake City and Santa Cruz Volunteers, May 21, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 9)
    - Bill O'Reilly (John Cusack interviewer), May 26, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 10)
    - Interview with Rev. Robin Hoover, June 3, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 11)
    - 5th Anniversary of Humane Borders, June 11, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 12)
    - Water Stations, September 21, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 13)
    - Nightly News - Last Stop, June 13, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 14)
    - A Walk in the Desert, July 1, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 15)
    - Methodist March for Migrants, July 14, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 16)
    - Annual Migrant Memorial, September 25, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 17)
    - Walking the Line, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 18)
    - Trip to Altar and Sasabe, October 23, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 19)
    - Dying to Get In, December 11, 2005 (Box 12, Othertype 20)
    - Sustainable Table, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 21)
    - Arizona Illustrated - Governors State of State, January 10, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 22)
    - 6th Annual March for Migrant, October 1, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 23)
    - Robin Hoover - Annoncing Mex. Trip, posters and maps, January 19, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 24)
    - Sue Goodman with Warning Poster, January 19, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 25)
    - Paul Fuschini Warning Posters, January 24, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 26)
    - Robin Hoover Map Project, January 26, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 27)
    - Religion and Ethics, February 26, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 28)
    - Robin Hoover comments on 4 migrant deaths, March 12, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 29)
    - Reaction to President, March 26, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 30)
    - Al Franken in Fresno, March 30, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 31)
    - World News - Border Walls, March 31, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 32)
    - Randall Pinkston Altar, Mexico, April 22, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 33)
    - Randall Pinkston Identifying Deceased, April 23, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 34)
    - Deadly Desert, May 7, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 35)
    - Response to President, May 15, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 36)
    - Response to Bush's visit to Yuma, May 18, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 37)
    - Migrant Trash, July 30, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 38)
    - Daybreak, June 14, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 39)
    - Minuteman Fence Vandalism at Palominas, Arizona, June 16, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 40)
    - 30 Days. Minuteman and Immigrant Family, July 1, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 41)
    - Immigration Debate, July 3, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 42)
    - Narco Corrido - Point of view, August 1, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 43)
    - Naomi's New Morning, August 13, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 44)
    - Migrant Memorial, October 1, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 45)
    - Premio Nacional de Derechos Humanos, December 13, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 46)
    - Robin Hoover Award at Los Pinos, Mexico City, December 13, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 47)
    - In the Shadow of the American Dream, December 26, 2006 (Box 12, Othertype 48)
    - Sanctuary, May 10, 2007 (Box 12, Othertype 49)
    - Invisible Chapel, 2007 (Box 12, Othertype 50)